all right I still don't know why you mm
caught on that I'm going line when I
don't have a thousand subscribers yeah
see it's the old technology guys figured
out the people's this house I'm living
it have this book and I'm totally
reading this I'm gonna read it to my kid
later but I will not read from here I'm
super excited for for it I just read
part of it gay bunnies love it anyway
not the point
watched Richard Wolf's video this
morning that he did a couple days ago or
he did a presentation that was recorded
on YouTube a couple days ago and like I
love him he's a brilliant man he totally
knows a lot about capitalism and how the
economy works as well as socialism in
the history of it I just don't think
that people from that generation
understand that we don't want the
repetition we don't want jobs we don't
want to trade for tea like that time
period has passed we can we don't want
to recreate the thing that you guys did
that was like a you work for 40 years
and then retire I mean that would have
been great because now we don't get that
right and we're like okay let's find
other we want to have a cat otos because
we get we're never going to get to
retirement there won't be any money left
the whole like the system doesn't
understand that people age if there's
aging bubbles like we just like basic
human stuff that we don't quite
comprehend as a as a society I love
worker cooperatives I think where
cooperatives are a great way for people
to come together and create a workplace
that they start this weird hair feeling
or you know that's actually that works
my brain likes to create things on my
body it's fun to me having a workers
cooperative is like I don't know how
he's proposing we get to all worker
cooperatives is it a government like the
government says now that we can only
have worker cooperatives so either
working by yourself if you have to hire
someone then they're now there do you
always have to happen there what about
subcontractor what if what if there's a
janitorial company that is a worker
cooperative and we want to hire them is
that okay because there were cooperative
as well what is and that's that those
things mean
worked oh those aren't like necessary
problem but like how do we get to
everyone to work or cooperative is it me
the consumer just decide we're not gonna
use anything that's not from worker
cooperative that's maybe the most
feasible way and that's never gonna
happen
there's a reason Walmart and Amazon are
successful because they're working
within our human nature we want cheap we
want best we want good and not the
worker cooperatives can't do those
things but they can't do all of those
things because it's just instead of
profit going to the shareholder it's
going to the workers and then there's
still the incentive to make yourself
work more and more and when you hire the
next person and is there seniority and
of course or not the companies aren't
asking to be able to bring anybody on if
they have when the workers do have more
empowerment there's at least more
options but eventually every industry
becomes a monopoly anyway and then you
don't have any other option so it's like
if everyone else in your workplace wants
to work for $20 an hour and work 80
hours a week and you can't work there
unless you do it then you have to do
that like that's and if everyone only
wants for 10 hours a week then you have
to do that because eventually each
industry is taken over by monopoly
because it would have to be because it's
like ok well we're in competition with
each other and so we're feeding off each
other or like eating up each other's
profits in competing so eventually why
aren't we just working together why
don't your workers and our workers team
up a now we're a bigger company which is
not necessarily benefiting the consumer
the consumer can come into play I said
are they but it just like it doesn't
solve it tells some of the problems in
the current system but it does not solve
enough of them like worker cooperatives
that were everywhere would have been an
amazing solution two decades ago we
don't want jobs anymore what we want is
purpose what we want is our needs met
what we want is to be happy to be
connected to be anything but right now
like I don't want to go to work five
days a week and trade time for money but
in no way sounds appealing to me I want
to spend my time doing what calls to me
in that day in that moment and in so
doing create a better world because
I'm living that life right now and that
is what happens hiss you from that space
create more awesomeness around you
you're more peaceful so and I'm in no
way peaceful all of the time but I look
for ways to help because I have that
little bit of extra energy because I'm
not working and I have way less energy
than most people which is why I'm not
working but having that I mean when you
give people the tools to create then
they create they don't need to be
employed in cooperatives in little
circles and are just able to do that and
if they have the ultimate power to be
able to transfer and choose other
circles like if you can work with two
people and you can work with a hundred
people all the same then there's gonna
be an advantage to working with a
hundred people that the two people
aren't gonna have but some people only
want to work in groups of two some
people don't want to have a conversation
with 10,000 people what we're gonna
create is going to be the consumer
cooperative because we only work in one
location
if we're lucky or unlucky depending on
your worldview whereas we buy things
from multiple companies and so for
buying things for multiple companies and
the consumers are the ones running the
company then we do create it for our own
individual needs it's not for the
pretend here's what we wish we wanted we
really wish everyone was doing great
it's like no how do we make sure like to
actually create a world we're looking
out your for your own self-interest is
actually looking out for everyone else's
self-interest because the more you're
able to coordinate and use your energy
in a way that you want to use it means
everyone gets to benefit from what
you're able to come up with from that
space and you're able to benefit from
everything everyone else is able to come
up with that in that space and working
with human nature is not everyone's
going to create not everyone is going to
be our version of what a worthy human
being is the solution to add is just
everyone's worthy No
is unworthy just because they're not my
version of worthy they set around in a
coach all day and play video games
it's basically what's what I do out of
necessity and without the video games
more watching television and was able to
come up with a system from that space
the solves all like dismantles
capitalism and solves all of our
problems and creates a world for
everyone just because it doesn't look
like you are being productive doesn't
mean you're not being productive it's
about looking inside if you'd like to I
feel pretty actually I'd like to I feel
like I'm an a contributing member and
I'm in a weird space we're both like oh
I get I do not look like I'm a
contributing member of society as much
as I wish I would I I have to work four
times as hard to look like I'm half as
far that is what having chronic illness
is and yet at the same time I'm like I'm
contributing amazingly I'm coming up
with I'm gifted like start the
revolution that saves the planet and
saves all of humanity and creates a
world for everybody who for everybody a
world that works for everybody and that
is so amazingly fun and exciting that
even if it never happens I get to
participate in the creation of like I
get to watch that happen in my mind I
get to watch oh yeah that's how we add
that that's how we add that that's how
we saw of that that's really cool when I
just allow my brain and body to do what
they what they will without society
dictating what's supposed to happen
magic happens we cannot and I'm
realizing how much I need to and I'm
just stopping being a video response is
starting just being a normal YouTube
live and just like update you all my
life that you don't care about because
you don't necessarily watch this but we
need to create better solutions we need
ways to collaborate and has to work for
everyone if it just works for the type-a
personality that's just like one of the
reasons I don't want worker cooperatives
is I can't work what worker cooperative
is gonna want me like it's like yes I
can work maybe when I'm doing really
great 10 hours a week can I live off of
ten hours a week no not when everyone
else is living 40 hours doing 40 hours I
can't make tables as fast as you I can't
do that that level of things and that
a new level of unfairness it's like yes
you're not selling milk to the guy who
has the kitten because he can pay the
most money and send to the children who
maybe have less money but it's more
worthy to go to children but it's still
like it's still broken because it's
still like right but if you can't work
40 hours a week or your cooperator then
you find a cooperative that works 20
hours right but your cooperative that is
only working 20 hours a week so all of
you are gonna be in the same boat so you
have diversity in the workplace and some
people can work five hours and some
people can work 60 hours and some people
can work who's gonna want to be a part
of that in that realm what I'm proposing
is you allow everyone to work what they
want to work therefore if you want to
work a zero you're gonna starve but like
you can work zero if you want to work 80
hours because you find your calling and
you're like all I want to do every day
all day we might have an intervention
for a little bit of balance in your life
and like okay how can we how come if
expecially if your mission is amazing
how can we how can we support you in
that how can we support you in your
mission how can we figure out how we
bring you food how we do these things if
your mission is so is something that
calls in other people but most people
are gonna be doing like mundane things
that are what they want to be doing and
from doing those mundane things amazing
stuff is gonna happen because you're
sitting around with your friends playing
a game or having a conversation over
beers and it triggers ideas especially
when you all have time and space to be
able to do anything it's not like oh I
have to work Monday to Friday it's like
oh we want to create that movie yeah
let's find the movie movie equipment and
the more that we own where things aren't
working and create the systems that work
the better like I don't know how they
think we're just gonna be able to create
worker cooperatives when we that's a
difficult process like that's not the
people I know who are in worker
cooperatives it's a lot of work and it's
a specific type of personality it's like
the community I'm currently house
sitting in if you want to live here this
is an amazing community your kid gets to
meet all these other people like it's
just everyone knows each other
we eat meals together if you don't want
to live here
this is Tork
like it's like I have to live with
people and they're gonna know about my
life and they're gonna like and there's
people who it's not quite that
dichotomous but like who one spouse is
like this is not my cup of tea
and another suppose just like this is
awesome and it works because then their
spouse is getting their needs met and so
even if you don't want to be here you're
getting your needs met but if you were
just forced to live in community because
that's what we've dictated is which is
kind of what a worker cooperative is
it's like you have to work there work
with other people wait are we less
racist are we less sexist are we less
homophobic did we figure out how to not
be so ablest against neurodiverse people
and people with with any kind of
physical condition because then we're
just gonna have in the
workforce like oh you didn't do enough
it's like do you know do you know what's
in my brain yeah I didn't physically
like yes I was procrastinating yes I was
doing that but then this amazing piece
came out of that it's like I did no work
all year but look I've been kind of the
best idea that was ever from this
company it's like right but we're firing
you because you didn't work in the way
that we thought you were gonna work I'm
just firing anything work when you work
in a workers cooperative I mean your
co-workers can decide to no longer have
you there generally but like where do
you go then you have to find all the
other misfits and do it I mean that's
kind of what I'm proposing but like in a
more structured basis of like right if
we're her cooperatives or what people
want they will naturally form around a
single project or an ongoing project and
be like yes this is what we've decided
this commitment is maybe you do need to
commit 60 hours a week to this one never
never shouldn't have to commit 60 hours
a week maybe you have to commit 30 hours
a week to this project in order to be a
part of it we want the top ten people on
it we don't want 30,000 people on it so
creating the infrastructure that is the
platform and the tech and just the apps
that help do that but help us understand
finance help us understand the stuff
that help us coordinate and say hey
here's what it takes to make a
cooperative check off these boxes go
through these steps who are your people
finding the people is a skill set and
what a lot of people don't have and so
how do you find those people it's like
I'd love to work in a workers
cooperative but they don't like me it's
like no someone likes you we will for
what do you want to do who are you we
can find you your people by creating the
algorithm that helps us do that just own
what works for you and what doesn't work
for you and be like I resonate with that
person or whatever your language is that
means that
that person drives me bananas but thank
God they do because I learned so much
from them when they do that that person
just know it's just toxic and if the
individual gets to decide those things
magic happens I'm just gonna keep saying
it like the head shake happens when you
help people tap into who they are give
them a space to contribute with the
tools that work for them in groups that
are not forced and are allowed to be
innovation occurs on this planet like
has never happened before and it's not
by going backwards and looking at like
we don't want jobs we don't I don't want
you to have to trade 40 hours one week I
might want to do one thing and one week
I want to do another thing and if I
commit to a project I'm committing to
that project and some people are gonna
commit to projects me like no and that's
their personality and we need to find
ways for them to contribute in a way
that works which might be coming in
doing the the brainstorming sparks right
in the beginning and then pulling out
and they go on to something else but the
more where you help them figure out that
that's their thing the more the rest of
us don't have to yell at them forever
like let your in and out cool awesome
you say you're gonna show up and then
you don't that is who you are
love yeah we're not gonna count on you
to be theirs if we need 10 bodies and
the seats you're not one of those bodies
were counting on and that doesn't make
them wrong for being that human being
and it doesn't make us wrong for Needy
them not to be like that human being
it's about creating a world that works
for everyone by owning where it doesn't
work for you as an individual and then
working with other people to make it
work it's a lot of and so that is what I
am doing and I'm living it and this week
I got like how much yes this is me I'm
going to be living it so and it's layers
so it's like a layer of leg okay
shedding the expectation of society says
and this is not how this should look and
this is not how you're not speaking it
right you're not able to think of the
words in the right order yeah that's how
my brain works you know what how it
works you came with an entire way to
dismantle capitalism and create a world
that works for everyone through
technology through workers can work at
home so we're talking about to a
consumer cooperative a tech consumer
cooperative a global tech platform that
we own together that we run together
we run with democracy and transparency
that no government currently has that
level of and then we create the
technology so a lot of the problems that
exist in the current government
structure can't exist in a corporate
like it's like we're both doing the
thing that's gonna save humanity and all
we're doing is tech so like what are you
gonna do right the platform didn't work
so we make a new one people didn't like
that so we make a new one
we're not dictating whether people get
one religion or another we're not
dictating whom people can marry we're
not saying portions right or wrong
although we're gonna be probably have
some thoughts on that and creating tools
around those those things we're having
the conversations and we're allowing the
diversity to happen on this planet you
don't get to control anyone else and
nobody else gets to control you and we
can create the tools to make that
feasible for the first time on our
planet it's actually doable to be to
look after both the individual and the
group by allowing the individual to be
an individual and finding groups that
they belong in instead of like oh you
were born in this group they better
accept you or you better conform to be
part of it it's like you can find your
own community that's like loves you for
you exactly as you are so then you get
to be who you are but that's not the
order it works in you be who you are and
then you find the people you work with
because they're not gonna know who you
are if you're not able to say oh this is
safe and that's why we're gonna start it
with that I'm showing up as me all of my
positives all of my negatives my
emotions my ideas I'm showing up as me
and it's gonna draw on the people who
want to work with me and those that tiny
group of the Word of Directors is going
to be our honest authentic selves and
work through our as much as
possible on camera for everyone to see
so that you all can participate and help
us not so you control us not so you can
critique every last thing that we do
because that is not we this is the world
we currently live in you do something
wrong and you're just done the world
it's gonna follow you to the end of time
that is not we need a safe space to make
messes and clean them up because that's
how we progress as a society by owning
what's not working and then making it
work and then owning what's not working
making work and try to see in beforehand
what's going to not work and mitigating
it before it ever happens and with
enough people it's mines work
on it and one focus platform to do that
with that is what we're gonna do and I'm
gonna keep showing up in a way that does
that and I'm gonna use YouTube because
its the potential to keep creating more
but I'm also on periscope because
sometimes I do I'm not going to come on
live four times a day on YouTube YouTube
doesn't like me going live so it doesn't
let me do it on the other version and
this is what I'm currently capable of
and I when you start tapping in to what
is easy and fun for you and find the
people that what is easy for fun than
them matches up what's not easy and fun
for you so together you're doing easy
and fun that is how we're gonna save the
planet because if it's hard if it's if
you have to be something that you
currently aren't in order to be able to
do it it is not gonna happen and
currently we're not really capable of
having worker cooperatives we're not
really like I am no except for the fact
I can't work but if I was gonna work to
be in a workers cooperative I would be
capable of the interpersonal skills to
be in a worker cooperative other people
are not capable of the interpersonal
skills but they're capable of the
physical work it will be torture to
force them to do that torture and I
think that we should not be doing that
so it's instead you want to create a
world that works for everyone
meaning you you want to help create a
world that works for you come on board
and speak for yourself come on board and
say this is where it doesn't work for me
and if what doesn't work for you is you
just don't want it to exist at all that
one we're not going to accommodate but
any other one of like oh this doesn't
work because this technology loud it's
too quiet it's too bright it stopped
right enough I don't like working in
groups I want to work by myself I don't
want to work well myself I want to work
in groups we can make it for everyone
technology gives us the capacity to be
able to do that and we're gonna have the
conversations I think that possible
there will be trade-offs there will be
things that are like we can't afford to
do everything for everyone all the time
right now right this is gonna be in
English because I speak English until we
can figure out how to make it in every
other language we're going to make it
accessible to my life which is pretty
accessible to most people's lives
because my life works
a very particular way but I can't think
of the way it works for absolutely
everyone unless other people aren't
bored being like here's where it doesn't
work for me like oh I do not think about
that because it worked for me in that
area where the world doesn't work for
you is one of your greatest gifts to
give the rest of the world because you
figure out why it's not working for you
and you help fix it you also fix it for
all the people it was working for you're
gonna create a system based on
cooperation that we don't even
understand because we've just been like
a living breathing competition for so
long but it's like oh if I succeed other
people fail yes in the current system
that is literally the definition
you cannot amass wealth without it
costing somebody else something in a new
system that's based on abundance and
innovation and like right you coming up
with an amazing idea is you come up with
an amazing idea I'm making it available
to everyone someone else being a better
artist better athlete better business
mind than you you get to reap what
they're sewing like you get to and you
still get to be your best athlete artist
businessperson bring you to the table
and when you start comparing yourselves
to everybody else and just be magic
happens
I just gotta keeps it like it's the best
feeling nothing else can replace it no
single relationship can replace it you
will give up everyone to hold on to that
feeling you don't have to luckily magic
happens also when people are attracted
to and the right people are attracted to
you and you feel love like never before
because you love yourself because you're
like oh I don't need the rest of you I
have me and look how many of you were
around this is awesome and everyone can
have that that's not something that
takes away from somebody else right me
being happy with who I am doesn't stop
you from being happy with who you are if
anything it gives you permission to be
happy about who you are me creating
ideas and abundance doesn't it take away
from your ideas and abundance only if
you allow it only if you're like oh
they're better than I am maybe if you
allow them to be and I'm living I'm
literally talking about this Olivia not
right now with my sister and I'm
processing it going through it and I
will I'll get through it and I'll be
back to love and back to truly believing
really we're equal
because it can fluctuates between like
you're the worst and have the best and
I'm here to stay at the planet you're
it's like kid neither of those things
are great I'm not better than and she's
not better than we are equal equally
worthy even if she can't see it and even
if I can't see it sometimes and so
universe is magic like when you open
yourself up to the the lessons that are
laid out for you to learn and that's
what we when he gives people the freedom
of life the freedom to not necessarily
work they have freedom to listen to
their inner voice to follow that path
and when people are following that path
or just better human beings they create
like never before they innovate like
never before on an individual basis then
when we group that together with other
people and we're all trying to create
that and we're creating the
conversations and we're having the
technology and the tools to be able to
do that that's the world I want to live
in so it's the world I'm gonna create
and if you want to come join come join
actually have some people viewing my
livestream would be awesome
I'll also if it depends which technology
I have available to me at the time so
our laptop looks like I can go live
until they fix that glitch if it's the
iPad then I cannot go live but I can
record and then post it and either way
I'm going to be doing it as me when
someone comes on board you can edit you
can edit it so we leave out all my arms
and aahs and things that don't make
sense to other people when I start one
train of thought and go onto the next
one
like I didn't finish that one here's my
finished thought someone can splice
those two together when other people are
capable of doing that and come on board
these will look better but right now
this is what it is and you doing what
you're capable of right now whether it's
in this project or outside is also
perfect I don't care if you can't edit I
don't care if you can't paint but you
want to paint paint I don't care if you
can't play an instrument using one
server but you want to play musical
instrument just play it and go get a
lesson because you probably gonna want
to I like what's out of it but like we
can create a world where everybody has
access to true abundance because most of
what is there is not you having a
doesn't take away from me there are some
finite resources on this planet where
yes if I have gold you don't get that
exact piece of gold but do you need it
do you what are you gonna do with the
gold what are you doing and we if we
look at the supply chain and say okay
but when I'm done with this gold when I
make it into something and then no
longer is needed in that purpose if we
can remount sit down and really claim it
there is no shortage there's only there
just is no shortage it's our mental
scarcity and it's the that is the issue
and together we can figure eight one did
is it really gold we need or do we just
want the gold is there something else we
can make that creates it that is
abundant can hemp use cuz hemp we can
grow all day every day we can use hemp
for whatever you were gonna use that for
you don't want a hemp engagement ring
whatever
we can create abundance together by only
where it's not if you're like I'm really
sad I don't get gold I'll let you have
Michael I don't care gold does not bring
me joy but I might want your kitten's
cuz like if your cat has kittens I don't
want Mike I don't wanna have a cat that
has kittens but I really want to play
with kittens so like share the abundance
in so many ways and every time so one
has thought these are kittens online I
can come over and play I never have
actually asked that but I'm like is
there not a kitten puppy just like play
place because that's what I want I don't
want to actually have a popular kitten
and right now I currently have a dog I'm
looking after and it's amazing but my
lifestyle isn't really conducive yet to
having a dog full-time because I've made
Cooper you're not allowed to have
housing when you have a dog so finding a
new house is way too stressful when you
have a dog don't have to get rid of it
and that would be heartbreaking anyway
we don't need to get into why I can't
have a dog
why did you ask why would you ask that
why would you trigger all of that this
is the world I live in all of my self in
isolation I could just have
conversations with myself and come up
with some amazing I talked to
myself in public because I'm pretty
awesome to talk to and I'm figuring this
out at the same time I'm figuring out
the project I'm figuring out who I am
and I show up in the world more
authentically and how I have achieved my
ex level of happiness and it in no way
looks what's up like what society says
society says it's like you're supposed
to own a house there's let's do this
you're supposed to like drive a car so
the employee
you're supposed to be healthy I'm like
not capable of any of that but when I am
capable of this I'm capable of living
life in an easy slow away and finding
infinite joy and learning in that every
interaction with other human beings
especially if they're negative like
especially if I they feel negative is
the greatest teacher on the planet being
a parent and constantly coming into
conflict is a greatest teacher this
morning my kid was playing with on the
other kids who she loves and it's the
one that's a little more um she will let
my kid get her way just cuz she's
younger and they're just like I set them
back they were yelling that was kind of
his like Oh yep my kid is getting used
to being around other people 24/7 and
she's got it figured I don't even know
that's what kind of what she wants cuz
she's an extrovert nobody is a hundred
percent wants to be around people all
the time so she's got to figure out how
to like be in this space for the next
month and anyway and she was like yeah I
get it
I I have people in my life who are also
like that and like we can have a
conversation and facilitate that
friendship and I have some ideas to
offer yes it's one it wasn't ever for it
wasn't like I know how to tell you and a
parent it was like it wasn't even an
offer and again it was like I would like
to I would like to talk about how we
facilitate their friendship and like was
which is an invitation is like could we
talk about that like yes I would love to
talk about that especially since it's
not my skillset and knowing this woman
it's absolutely her school looking
at her kid and how she's raised her kid
like yep love it and also no idea how to
reproduce that nor will I reproduce it
because it's she's here to do her thing
and she's here to raise her kid and her
way but the more I can pick up stuff
that does work that's what community is
and I'm gonna be here for a month and
just like soaking it all in the good the
bad a little bit meanwhile I went off on
some tangents this was totally about
workers cooperatives come like subscribe
check that little bells he can come on
live when when I'm online we can have
the real discussions I'm working on
crystallizing the first the first
project the one that's going to be
social media ish platform it is going to
bring us so much connection and movement
forward and I only first heard about it
on
Sunday what day is today Friday so it's
less than a week old and I'm like that's
how I know it was someone on my
periscope oh love it love it it's roll
cafes and somebody else wants to look
that up and figure that out but like
creating that infrastructure to do that
online on a massive scale is exactly
that's why how my brain works so it's
it's in the process and then finding the
people to do that with which is not how
my brain works but other people are
coming on board that are that and we
cannot do this under the old paradigm we
have to do it transparently we have to
do it authentically as our unique selves
because if I have to be professional and
work with a bunch of other stuff e suits
to do this it is not happening if other
people have to like participate and
troll and it's not happening and which
is why we're not creating that we don't
need to allow that we do not need to
allow the trolls to exist in our space
to have it doesn't mean we don't allow
dissent
we encourage dissent just not trolls
just not the leg I'm gonna disagree just
to disagree which is what I do but like
naturally and authentically you give me
a I'm gonna tell you B if you give me B
I can tell you a it's just how it works
but I know that now it's like a be like
take a moment maybe they don't need to
hear that side of it maybe your middle
child peacekeeper slash instigator
doesn't need to roll out and do all of
that so around for 30 minutes now and
I'm gonna go I'm still II tried the blog
post for Monday at some point and this
thing is so close to happening I can
feel it in like every one of my cells
and I'm letting go of the like that I
know how this is gonna happen cuz every
time like this is how this is gonna
happen I'm gonna go on YouTube people
are gonna come on it's gonna go viral
and then that both terrifies me and
excites me then it doesn't happen I get
disappointed and I'm like oh it's like
right that's not just listen go on
YouTube that's all you have to do
whatever happens isn't up to you you
don't have any say over it so just go on
listen to the inner voice and follow it
and I'm getting now not right now but
over the last week how much that is just
as important as the global cooperative
be how I'm managing to figure out who I
am to do the thing to create the global
cooperative is just as much what I have
to offer as the co-operative itself both
because then it energizes me to be
surrounded by people that are like that
and also like it's
amazing if listen to your inner voice
I'm gonna end all of it
anyone follow that you know would like
to come work with me get in contact
there's an email somewhere if not it is
collaborative democracy at gmail.com
which is my 1 for this project and you
can also just I think you can message on
YouTube message for comment below
comment below because I'm so well
unknown that I see every comment and if
my social anxiety is not kick in
especially if you ask a question I will
answer it cuz questions I like to answer
whereas comments I'm like wait why
comment what do I call me back I once I
know something I do better and I'm doing
better every time and there is no need
to do better you get to be you as you
are exactly now without any mean to
improve in doing that you naturally
improve I don't I don't know what kind
of magic I tapped into but if I can
bottle it you all we're just gonna
create a world that is most its abundant
and peaceful for everyone and it's not
even like it could happen it's going to
happen like every step along the way
because we're gonna fail in the right
direction I'm failing in the right
direction as a single individual person
like right stumbled on those words not
editing this might be a disaster so
might come on and be like you said this
he was super offensive then I go viral
for the wrong reasons and really let's
talk about some a piece of I'll be
like really new to me
may could be what happens if the
universe intends that it'll happen and
I've learned from that like it's just
riding this rollercoaster and allowing
it to process and not getting anxious
about every step along the way even
though I kind of know every step along
the way for the big project no that's
not sure I know like the bones of it
other people need to fill in the other
pieces button why don't you go for
shower I'm gonna go walk through the
communities and hear people talking and
I want to be with people then I'm gonna
come back on and chat with other people
not on here on periscope alright take
care of YouTube world like and subscribe